Dead man's hand.
Aces and eights.
Unbelievable.
These card's must
owe you money. Mr. Meech.
Just lucky. I guess.
It's nearly midnight.
You should get some sleep.
Big day tomorrow.
Once more around.
Calms my nerves.
Yeah. fine.
This is what they mean
by sunk cost.
Shift change?
Too early.
Secure the witness.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
How are you. agent?
Just me.
AUSA Rothbart.
Everything OK?
I just need to go over a few
final details with my witness
before tomorrow.
Of course. sir.
He's back here.
We'll just be in the living room.
Mr. Meech.
What the hell is this?
Son of a bitch.
Gun!
OpCen. shooter inside.
One agent down.
Agent Litman. report back.
What happened?
Kenya?
Hello? Hello?
Are you all right?
Hello?
Agent Zidan.
Copy that.
I'm on the way.
Been a while since we've done
a graveyard shift.
What'd Gemma say
when you were sneaking out?
Uh. she didn't wake up.
Yeah. OK.
you're a giant...
big-ass feet clomping around.
It's midnight. Maggie.
Some people sleep.
Thanks for getting here so fast.
It's a nightmare.
Two of my best agents
on protective detail
plus the witness. Cordell Meech.
He's supposed to testify
in a grand jury in the morning.
Someone came here
to make sure he wouldn't talk.
Who knew about this location?
Just us and the
U.S. Attorney's Office.
This was kept quiet.
Well. the only shell casings
I'm seeing are from our agents.
This guy cleaned up
after himself.
Who called it in?
Agent Kenya Litman over there.
Dispatcher heard
a guy on the line.
We assume the killer was
still inside.
He didn't break in.
He didn't try to disable
the cameras either.
No. We haven't seen
or watched the footage yet.
It's all yours.
OK. so our witness was
shot point-blank.
our agents were over here
aimed in that direction.
Whoever killed them...
Our agents let them in.
All right. folks.
I know it's late.
but. uh. 41 minutes ago.
a federal whistleblower
named Cordell Meech
was murdered in FBI custody
along with two agents from
the Bureau's Security Division.
Cuts deep when
we lose any of our own.
so let's step it up tonight for
Kenya Litman and Richard Brown.
All right.
let's talk about Mr. Meech.
Cordell Meech was set to be
questioned before a grand jury
in less than eight hours.
He was an accountant
for WellReach Health.
an NGO that provides
free anti-malarial meds
for sub-Saharan Africa.
WellReach Health recently
lost their government funding.
right?
Yes. though it wasn't political.
An accusation was made
of a corporate loophole
being used to possibly
launder money. thus the probe.
Right. Well. we...
we need to dig into that.
But we eyes-up on the safehouse
security cameras?
Yes. sir.
Just got the feed.
Looks like we got a pizza
delivery guy at 9:02 p.m.
Doesn't enter.
Just stands in the doorway.
hands them the pizza.
Right. OK.
11:48 p.m..
this guy shows up.
OK. yeah.
That's a good enough angle
for facial rec.
Uh. no.
that's AUSA Meyer Rothbart.
Well. it makes sense
that he'd be there.
Rothbart's leading
the grand jury.
Though it's pretty late
for a witness debrief.
- Yeah. this is weird.
- What?
The emergency call to
dispatch came in at 11:51 p.m.
AUSA Rothbart was still inside.
OK. we... we definitely
did not find Rothbart's body
at the scene of the crime.
right?
No. look.
A minute later.
just strolls out the front door.
So Rothbart was still
inside the safe house
when the murders happened.
That would mean...
We are not saying
a New York AUSA
gunned down his own witness
and two of our agents...
yet.
We need to talk
to Meyer Rothbart.
Where is he now?
It's almost 1:00 a.m.
Phone's pinging
at his home address.
Send a team.
Did you ever see
anything like this when
you were a prosecutor.
attorney just snaps.
kills his own witness?
Can't say that I have.
Let's hope there's
another explanation.
Hello?
AUSA Meyer Rothbart. FBI.
Mr. Rothbart?
Anybody home?
Eva. you're gonna
want to see this.
Oh.
That's Rothbart. all right.
So what are we seeing here?
That an AUSA
kills his star witness?
And rather than go down for it.
he decides to take his own life?
- I don't know.
I'm not so sure.
There's no powder burns.
Look at the bloodstains.
It's dark at the edge
like he's been here a while.
That's full rigor.
Yeah.
Jubal. we found
Meyer Rothbart dead
from an apparent
self-inflicted gunshot wound.
Now. I'm no ME...
this guy's definitely been here
for at least seven hours.
When did you say your witness
was killed again?
Yeah. 57 minutes ago.
There's no way Rothbart
could have been our shooter.
- All right.
What the hell's going on?
Somebody help me out.
If AUSA Rothbart died
seven hours ago.
then how the hell did he show up
in high-def resolution
at that safe house?
You know what?
Run it back.
Here you go.
- I mean. right?
It looks like Meyer Rothbart.
Did you run it
through facial rec?
Just did.
- And?
- 63% match.
- 63. huh?
That's not a home run.
Let's head down another road.
see where it takes us.
What if somebody
killed Rothbart.
tried to make it look
like suicide?
And then what.
assumed Rothbart's identity
so they could gain access
to a federal safe house
and silence a star witness?
It sounds insane. but it fits
the current fact pattern.
Hey. guys.
Rothbart's car just pinged
on a traffic cam.
- OK.
- Three minutes ago. Look.
- All right. Can you zoom in?
- Yeah.
I mean. sure looks like him.
What is going on here?
Let's get a team on that car.
There it is.
Jubal. we found Rothbart's car.
No sign of him. though.
- Wait.
Is that him?
Looks like
he's stealing another car.
♪ Bad. bad. bad. bad news
♪ I'm going to take you down ♪
There.
♪ Some bad. bad. bad.
bad news ♪
Split up.
You want a piece of this.
tough guy?
You want a piece of this?
My bad.
Let's go!
Come on!
Yes! Nice!
Good to see you again.
Agent Bell.
Don't move.
OA.
I know who we're chasing.
It's Oslo.
He's back.
Burning the midnight oil?
Oh. so you heard the news.
What. that Oslo. a contract
killer wanted by Interpol
in six countries.
including our own.
just washed up on our shores?
Well. we're on it.
Oh. that's what
you said last time
when he murdered a U.S. senator
and a well-respected CEO.
He will not get away again.
That's why I'm here
at 1:30 in the morning.
to make sure that he doesn't.
All due respect. Anna. I am
running this investigation.
Oslo has murdered VIPs
all over the globe.
My people consider him
an invaluable asset.
He has state secrets that we
would love to get our hands on.
Anna. I don't pretend
to know what it is you want.
but this one is on my turf.
So you can either help
or step aside.
All right. listen up.
Anna Vorpe will be coming
on board to lend a hand.
So what have we got?
So we know Oslo's
been in disguise
all night as AUSA Rothbart.
We think he'll shed it
if he hasn't already.
But thankfully.
we know what he looks like now.
His face is in our system.
so the manhunt is on.
And NYPD has joined in.
so has U.S. Marshals.
And DHS is monitoring ports
and airstrips.
I brought NSA up to speed
there on signals intelligence.
Very good.
This hit on Cordell Meech
has something to do
with the grand jury hearing.
Someone hired Oslo
to silence their star witness.
so who's to say that
Oslo's job is done?
Right. right. right.
So who are the other witnesses
that are expected
to testify in six hours?
One is Elliot Griffin.
the locations manager
for WellReach Health.
The second is Lynette Caddick.
the CFO for the company.
Yeah. but Meech was
the whistleblower.
He was the only witness
in FBI protective custody.
Means these two
are sitting ducks.
Well. wake them up.
Let them know
our agents are coming by
to bring them to 26 Fed.
I'm not liking this one bit.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go around the corner.
- Yeah.
Man approaching with a weapon.
- Hey. hey. hey.
Elliot.
- Get out of here! Go!
- Elliot. stop.
- FBI!
- Easy. easy.
Put the bat down now.
My name is Special Agent Scola
with the FBI.
This is my partner.
Special Agent Ramos.
You scared the crap out of me.
It's 3:00 in the morning. man.
Look. Mr. Griffin.
we're sorry to alarm you.
but we're here because
we believe that
there's a credible threat
against your life
regarding a testimony
that you're supposed to give
in a couple hours.
My life?
It's an accounting trial.
You need to come with us
right now.
Yeah. pack a bag.
everything you might need
for the next 24 hours.
'cause you won't be coming home
before the grand jury.
Let's go.
Hey. Anna.
I just got off the phone with
the criminal division chief.
Man was in shock.
Rothbart had been with the
Eastern District for 16 years.
Mm. So are they gonna push
for a postponement?
Turns out no.
They don't want to delay
the grand jury.
He's going to assign another
senior attorney to the case.
And...
- Even after
the last one was murdered?
We will not be intimidated
into silence.
No. we will not.
Um. and what about
the other witnesses?
Uh. yeah. they're en route.
OK.
Will you let me know
when they get here?
Yeah.
Hell of a night.
Yeah. I'm. uh.
running on pure adrenaline.
What are you working on?
Peeling back the onion.
Do you need a sounding board?
Sure.
We know Oslo
is motivated by money.
but he's just a weapon put
in play for the right price.
The real question is who would
want to derail the grand jury?
You're asking who's the target.
Right.
Someone with the finances
to afford Oslo's services.
Exactly.
WellReach Health
gets a lot of its funding
from CSR programs
and philanthropic grants.
so maybe we look into
the donor lists?
Or what if the mastermind
behind this attack
has been under our nose
the whole time?
The CFO of WellReach Health?
Lynnette Caddick.
She just bought a vacation home
Upstate right on the water.
8 million.
For 8 million.
I'd expect the Hamptons.
Misappropriation
of government funds?
Well. it certainly tracks.
She's here.
I'm gonna go help Jubal
wrangle the witnesses.
Ready to meet the boss?
This is our ASAC.
Jubal Valentine.
- Hello.
Welcome. ma'am.
This is ridiculous.
I demand to be placed
into Witness Protection.
If there's been a threat
on my life...
You're safe here.
Ms. Caddick. I assure you.
He's right.
Nobody gets into 26 Fed
unless they're invited.
You'll be sequestered here
until the grand jury
and then remain in protective
custody for the next 24 hours.
Where are we taking her?
We're going to
the conference room on 20th
and Officer Ramsey
will stay with her there.
Thanks.
Thank you. ma'am.
OK.
- Next up.
- Yeah.
Uh. welcome. Mr. Griffin.
You're safe now.
Uh. you'll be going to
the fourth floor.
Meyers will stay close
for your protection.
Uh. hang on.
Uh. if... if... if someone's
going after the witnesses.
Lynette's in danger.
- No. she's here already.
She's safe.
Can I see her?
I mean. this has all been
so crazy. man.
Well. procedure requires
we keep you separated
before the grand jury to avoid
any appearance of collusion
before your testimonies.
- OK. yeah.
- OK?
- Thanks.
This fine gentleman will
take you to the fourth floor.
Thanks. Myers.
- You're welcome.
You want to come with me?
- All right.
You guys mind getting a start
on a communication with SI-OC.
just giving them
a status report?
- Yeah. we can do that.
- OK. Thank you.
- You got it.
- OK.
- Two for two.
Not bad.
Yeah.
Well. we're definitely
not out of the woods.
Oslo is not giving up
his next opportunities
when we move the witnesses
to the courthouse.
I'll wrangle
with the folks at JSOC
for an intel assessment.
I can give you guys
the safest route.
- OK. yeah.
That'd be great.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
- See you around. Valentine.
- Yeah.
Don't say
I never gave you anything.
Officer Juerez.
requesting status update.
We have an FBI
police officer down
in the west garage stairwell.
send a team ASAP.
Meyers. are you still with
the witness. Elliot Griffin?
Meyers?
Meyers. do you read me?
OK.
Hey. Oslo's here.
He's in the building.
Alert Lynette Caddick's detail.
He's coming for her next.
- He's here.
Oslo is in the building.
He's already killed
Elliot Griffin.
and he's going after
Lynette Caddick next.
Initiate
a building-wide lockdown.
Restrict all elevator access
and seal every exit.
And I want FBI police
at both of these JOC doors.
- I'll notify our agentS.
- No. no. no. no. no.
Oslo stole Meyer's radio
and his employee access badge.
We need to stay off the comms.
Assume he can hear us.
I want a private
tactical channel with our team.
- On it.
- Deactivate that stolen badge.
We can't have Oslo with
full access to this building.
- Yeah.
Copy that.
How the hell did he get inside?
That's the
million-dollar question.
OK. I got the feed
from the parking garage.
He chokes out our officer
in the stairwell
and finishes the job.
I want teams
combing all lower floors.
No one goes alone.
Who's got the fourth floor feed?
I'm up on it.
- All right.
Scrub back.
Let's see what
we're up against here.
There you go.
He just took a picture.
When was this?
Not even six minutes ago.
Where's my private channel?
Uh. it's up.
They've all switched
to channel three.
- Channel three.
All right. listen up.
From this point on.
we only use this channel.
Our comms have been compromised.
Oslo is in the building.
He's already executed
two of our officers
and Elliot Griffin.
Copy. We'll start
clearing the lower floors.
- OK. great.
Maggie. OA.
he'll be headed to Lynette next.
Oh. we just left her.
O-OK. well. get back there
and move her
to a more secure room
and strongpoint that location.
Copy that.
They're not in here.
Jubal. conference room is empty.
Are we too late?
Hang on.
- FBI!
Drop your weapon!
- Ramsey. it's us.
- Take it easy.
Where's Lynette?
She's with me.
- Come on.
Come over here.
We have the witness.
You told me I'd be safe here.
I'm not gonna let anything
happen to you.
All right. Maggie and OA have
Lynette Caddick.
They're moving her off of 20.
Then where the hell is this guy?
We're scanning every
live feed in the building.
but it's like Oslo
just vanished.
- Well. keep your eyes peeled.
He is definitely here.
All right. he's got to know
we're on to him.
so he'll be
avoiding the cameras.
This is 26 Fed.
There's only so many places
you can hide.
Wait.
Got him.
- OK. Where is this?
- On floor 15.
Well. that's only five floors
below Maggie and OA.
They're gonna need someone
to run interference.
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
Scola. Eva. listen up.
Oslo has already made it to 15.
What's your location?
We're still down on 10.
- All right. Get to 15.
Uh. use stairwell A.
But remember.
Oslo has already killed
three people in this building.
Please be careful.
We're on our way.
- Boss?
- Yeah?
- We got bigger problems.
- Talk to me.
Oslo just ducked into
an office on 15 and...
look.
What?
What is he doing?
He's making a torch.
Pretty clever.
If this works...
We just lost the feed.
Every camera's down
on that floor.
He's covering his movements.
Eva. Scola. heads up.
Oslo used the building's
fire suppression system
to take out the cameras on 15.
so you're on your own
until we get the feeds back.
Over here.
- Hey.
- I was just trying
to get someplace safe.
Jubal. medical to 15.
We have an individual
with a gunshot wound.
Hey. let's look at this. OK?
- All right.
Good news... it's not fatal.
There's no way
Oslo missed that shot.
You're right.
He wanted us to find her.
He's diverting us.
Ma'am. did you see
which way he went?
- That way.
Back that way.
- All right.
I'm gonna cut him off.
Oslo. drop your weapon!
Got shots fired. stairwell C.
Oslo near 19.
I'm in pursuit.
- 19th floor.
- Yeah. pulling up 19th floor.
Maggie. OA. did you hear that?
Oslo is now one floor
below you near stairwell C.
OK. moving up.
- Yeah.
- OK.
Uh. west elevators are clear.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. you know what?
We're gonna send
the west elevator to you.
Get on and we'll
bring you up to us.
- Copy.
We're gonna turn around.
Let's go.
Ramsey. watch our six.
Jubal. we're here.
We're easy targets.
Yeah. elevator's almost to you.
Hang in there.
Come on. let's go. let's go.
Jubal. we're in.
The grand jury's in five hours.
We'll get you there.
This is karma.
Cover her.
Jubal. I think Oslo might
be on top of our elevator.
Get us out of here now.
Copy.
Override the door to open them.
Get them out of there.
- Doing it now.
Ramsey.
Go.
You go first.
I'll cover.
Come on.
- OK.
- I got you.
OK.
- Get her out of here!
Go. go!
Jubal. OA's stuck
in the elevator with Oslo.
- What?
What the hell happened?
The override bucked... we have
to get it to a program floor.
Get it to this floor!
Scola. Eva.
get to the 31st floor
of the West elevator bank!
Go! To the elevator bank! Go!
- I'm on it.
Now! Run!
Threat's contained.
Agent Zidan. back on your feet.
Amazing recovery
from my Novichok.
You had to know that you
were gonna fail today. Oslo.
Is that right?
We have your face now.
your biometrics. your prints.
You are not just in our system.
but every law enforcement
agency in the country
is looking for you.
We know you make
20 million per hit.
This was a risky job.
breaking into
the FBI field office.
Had to have been more.
So who has the resources
to get your attention?
What makes you think I'd know?
Uh. w-well.
this... this testimony
you're supposed to give
for WellReach in a few hours.
why...
why don't we start with that?
I was planning to invoke
my Fifth Amendment rights
tomorrow.
I won't incriminate myself
to the FBI.
Lynette.
I am willing to offer you
a limited use immunity.
That means that whatever
you say in this interview
cannot be used against you.
And we are obviously
all in a jam here.
so please. tell us who
would want to silence you
and the other witnesses.
I don't know their identity.
- Hmm.
How convenient.
Most clients demand anonymity.
but this client
was beyond careful.
Real tradecraft.
Non-existent digital footprint.
The payment method
was sophisticated.
- Untraceable.
Got it.
I believe they work
for the United States military.
A lobbyist emailed me
19 months ago.
said they were from
a hush-hush firm in the city.
They wouldn't tell me
which one. but
they wanted me to start
a money laundering scheme
to move cash offshore.
And as an NGO. WellReach
would make the perfect vehicle.
I told him to take a hike.
I... I had no interest
in committing financial fraud.
But then I...
They told you what
your cut would be?
15%.
And they needed
to launder millions.
More money than I had ever seen.
So you took the payout.
you looked the other way.
I knew what I was doing
was wrong. but it was...
it was... it was just paperwork.
It was just spreadsheets.
numbers.
It... it wasn't hurting anyone.
But one day. I got curious
and started digging
and traced the money
to a front in Ramadi.
I-Iraq?
This isn't the first time
this client has
employed my services.
All targets
I've eliminated for them
seem to benefit U.S. interests.
And the language they use.
tactical jargon.
uniquely military.
What was the lobbyist's name?
- We don't know.
We never met in person.
We only communicated
over secure email.
Tell us their name.
Tribune.
At least that's what
they told me to call him.
It's a code name. I know.
but it's all I have.
Why are you telling us
everything?
Tribune abducted my daughter.
Imogen.
That's the only reason I agreed
to return to this country.
She's here. and I won't
let her die because of me.
Now you want our help?
Agent Bell.
the reason I let you live.
because I knew if I failed
in my mission tonight.
you would follow the breadcrumbs
and you would save
my little girl.
We don't need to listen to this.
Wait.
My real name...
is Daniel Pierce.
My work takes me
all across the globe.
But Imogen is my only home.
She's all I have.
I can't let her die.
Did your daughter know what
you do for a living?
Have you ever kept something
from somebody you love
just to protect them?
Find my daughter.
and you will find Tribune.
Where are we with
verifying Oslo's story?
There is an Imogen Pierce
studying at NYU.
She's 21. a British national.
Just called her RA.
She hasn't been back
to her dorm in two days.
- OK. so she's missing.
Timeline tracks.
Oslo is fully cooperating.
He gave Maggie and OA the
password to his burner phone
and it turns out
there's a private text thread
between Oslo and Tribune.
Looks like after every murder.
Oslo would update Tribune by
sending a proof of death photo.
Well. that's Elliot Griffin
and our whistleblower.
And then there's this.
That's Imogen Pierce.
So Oslo is telling the truth.
Tribune is holding his daughter
as a bargaining chip.
Can we trace Tribune's number?
- I already tried.
It's protected by the
same enhanced encryption
our military uses.
Well. that's consistent
with Oslo's theory.
Whoever Tribune is.
we are unmasking them now.
So how do we flush them out?
Tribune's orders were clear.
Kill these witnesses or you'll
never see your daughter again.
- But Oslo failed.
Lynette Caddick's still alive.
But no one outside of 26 Fed
knows that.
To save this girl
and identify Tribune.
we just have to make him
believe Oslo succeeded
in killing all three witnesses.
- All right.
Put out a BOLO.
Oslo escaped 26 Fed
after murdering three people.
including Lynette Caddick.
Now we just have
to kill Lynette Caddick.
Yeah.
Looks dead enough to me.
So as far as Tribune knows.
the hit on Lynette
was a success.
Yeah. now we just
have to wait to see
if he holds up
his end of the deal.
Oh. wait. Hang on.
It's in code.
I don't know.
It's a bunch of letters
and then one word... daybreak.
'Cause why would this be easy?
Well. the key could be
any word in any language.
Good thing we have a shortcut.
I told you everything I know.
I highly doubt that.
Ah.
The indecipherable cipher.
What's the key word?
I wish to see my daughter
one last time.
I need to tell her
that I'm sorry.
Deal.
What's the key word
to unlock the cipher?
Her name. of course.
Imogen.
- All right.
Eyes up. people.
So the location
Tribune texted for the drop
was encrypted with
a Vigenère cipher.
The shared keyword is his
daughter's first name. Imogen.
- Vigenère cipher.
- Yeah.
Used that back in the Civil War.
- Here we go.
- What did we get?
- It's a location.
- Yeah?
OK.
Listen up. all teams.
We believe Tribune
will be arriving
at the Brooklyn dry docks
at daybreak.
We don't know what
he looks like.
we don't know if he'll be
showing up with the hostage.
All we know for sure is
we will be there waiting.
so you have 40 minutes
to get to those docks.
Set up and get invisible.
Let's go.
- Dock's clear.
Nothing yet.
What's going on with you?
Just been dreaming about the
day we were gonna catch Oslo.
It all just seems a little...
Hollow?
Yeah.
He's just a weapon. a tool.
And these people that
put him to work.
these powerful people.
they think that the law
doesn't apply to them.
- Yeah.
That's true.
But I don't think that's
what's going on with you.
Really. that's it?
Scola. Eva. anything yet?
All is quiet.
except for the gulls.
All right. guys.
Heads up.
We got a sedan entering
the lot at pier nine.
Jersey plates.
Oscar-seven-alpha-
two-delta-one.
All right. run it.
Plates were reported
stolen two days ago.
Dead end.
I can't see the driver.
Can you guys see his face?
Looks like a male. mid-50s.
That could be our guy.
OK. remember
that we need confirmation
that the girl is in the car
before we move.
There she is.
All right. guys.
we got eyes on Imogen.
She's in the back seat.
- It's got to be Tribune.
All agents. move in.
Remember.
the girl is a priority.
We're primary.
Scola. you go deep.
Step out of the car
with your hands up.
- Shots fired.
Suspect down.
Imogen?
Special Agent Bell.
Are you hurt?
No.
Where's my dad?
He said he'd be here.
Is he in trouble?
We're gonna take you to him.
Guys?
OpCen. roll an ambo over here.
Tribune needs medical attention.
I'm not Tribune.
Somebody help me out here.
That driver is not Tribune.
Who the hell is he?
Facial rec ID'd him
as Mike Hecksher. 55.
originally from Columbia City.
Indiana.
Does he have a record?
Uh. Hecksher was a Marine.
Then he joined a unit
called Task Force Copper.
rotated home in 2018.
Task Force Copper?
That's an
intelligence support activity.
Where was Hecksher deployed?
Uh. Iraq.
Do we have anything
more specific?
Looks like Ramadi.
That's the city where
Lynette Caddick claims
the laundered money went to.
- Right.
Go. Maggie.
Jubal. we were just
going through
Hecksher's personal effects.
and there's a photo
in his wallet
you're gonna want to see.
OA's sending it to you now.
Uh. yeah. I got it.
Looks like Hecksher's
task force.
taken somewhere
in the Middle East.
And. uh.
there's a familiar face.
Hey.
Saw the BOLO.
Looks like Oslo managed to evade
your crack team once again.
Mm.
Don't believe
everything you read.
The grand jury hearing.
our murdered witnesses
from WellReach Health.
even Oslo.
they were all part
of a much bigger coverup.
all set in motion by you.
What I couldn't quite
put my finger on was why.
And then I remembered a story
about a Task Force Copper op
that went sideways in Iraq.
Ramadi. to be exact.
It was supposed to be
a quiet snatch and grab.
but it turns out
the intel was bad.
16 Iraqi civilians were killed
by U.S. forces.
a geopolitical nightmare
if it were to ever come out.
But. of course. it didn't.
Because you laundered money
through WellReach
and used it to pay the locals
in exchange for their silence.
But you got desperate.
The grand jury
would expose everything.
You even leveraged Oslo
to take out anyone
who could tie you
to the cover up.
You let him into 26 Fed
to finish the job.
We stopped him.
And now. I am going to stop you.
You brought your game
into my backyard.
and good people died.
This ends with you
in front of a judge.
You should probably get that.
- Yes. sir?
How can I help you?
Hey. Isobel. I've got somebody
from the SecDef's office
asking for a word.
Gonna punch you over to them.
SAC Castille.
this is Assistant Secretary
of Defense Joe Kiernan.
Yes. sir?
What your team achieved
in the past 24 hours.
finally apprehending Oslo.
is an incredible victory.
but Ms. Vorpe is critical
to the national security
of the homeland.
I... I disagree.
Well. that's noted.
But she walks.
Who are you really?
Have a good day. Isobel.
- Well. I'm still wired.
Anybody want to get breakfast?
Unless it involves a booster
seat and Cheerios. I'm out.
I gotta take over for Nina
with Dougie.
Eva. what about you?
Uh. I'd love to.
but I think I could still
make it to kickboxing.
- All right. see ya.
- See ya'll later.
I'm in.
Wanna call Gemma
and see if she can make it?
- Uh. that's the thing.
Gemma's not at home.
Oh. like. business trip?
We're not together anymore.
- What?
Since when?
A few months ago.
A few months ago?
I knew something was up
with you.
I was waiting for you
to let me in.
Well. that seems to be
a recurring theme with me.
I wanted to tell you.
but if I did.
it was gonna make it real.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Pancakes are on me.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-